#### FRONT-END DEVELOPER



## Nenad Marinković

Leopoldine-Schlinger-Gasse 4/21, 1020 Wien nenadmarinkovic.com nenadmarinkovic@protonmail.com

+43 670 558 32 82

Citizenship: Serbian
An EU-Family member with unrestricted access to the job market.

#### **PROFIL**

Web developer with a focus on front-end, experienced in all stages of web development, with a strong passion for all web-related programming languages and technologies, particularly:

JavaScript, React, Vue.js, Next.js, Gatsby, CSS, Sass, different CSS-in-JS solutions, Git (Github and Gitlab), content management systems (Wordpress and headless CMS), web accessibility, animations, UI/UX, Figma, Jira.

Back-end solid foundations: Node, PHP, MySQL, MongoDB, data structures.

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

04/2022 - 09/2023

Software Developer, Front-end
DCCS IT Business Solutions, Vienna and Graz

Web front-end development with Vue.js, HTML, CSS, PHP, Sass, JavaScript, jQuery, Liferay, Figma, Visual Studio.

dccs.eu

01/2021 - 12/2021

## Front-end developer

### abss interactive GmbH, Vienna, Austria

Web front-end development with React, Next.js, HTML, CSS, Sass, JavaScript, jQuery, Gulp, Wordpress, SVG animations, web accessibility, newsletter templates, PHP, MySQL, Git, BitBucket, Figma, Adobe Photoshop, Visual Studio Code.

abss.at

12/2019 - 11/2020

## Front-end developer

## Popart Studio, Novi Sad, Serbia

Web front-end development with HTML, CSS, Sass, JavaScript, jQuery, Gulp, Wordpress, Drupal, SVG animations, PHP, MySQL, Git, Figma, Adobe Photoshop.

popwebdesign.net popwebdesign.de

06/2019 - 07/2019

## Web development Internship

## Vega IT, Novi Sad, Serbia

Web front-end development internship with HTML, CSS, SCSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Gulp, Adobe Photoshop.

vegaitglobal.com

01/2017 - 11/2019

# IT Recruiter and Talent Advocate Visage.jobs, Remote

Looking for talents and connecting employers and developers especially in IT industry.

visage.jobs

11/2016 - 08/2017

Web content writer

Four Dots, Novi Sad, Serbia

Writing content marketing for websites ang blogs about different topics.

fourdots.com

#### **AUSBILDUNG**

2011 MA Political Sociology

University of Belgrade, Faculty of Political Sciences.

2007 **BA Sociology** 

University of Niš, Faculty of Philosophy

#### **LANGUAGES**

English - C1

German - B1

Serbian (BHS) - native

#### **HOBBYS**

Hiking, cycling, gym trainings, reading, traveling.